<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="first_attraction">First Attraction</string>
    <string name="second_attraction">Second Attraction</string>
    <string name="third_attraction">Third Attraction</string>
    <string name="fourth_attraction">Fourth Attraction</string>
    <string name="fifth_attraction">Fifth Attraction</string>
    <string name="sixth_attraction">Sixth Attraction</string>
    <string name="first_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="second_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="third_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="fourth_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="fifth_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="sixth_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="seventh_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="eighth_thing">You Can Visit</string>
    <string name="capri">Capri (usually pronounced /kəˈpriː/ by English speakers; Italian pronunciation: [ˈkaːpri]) is an island located in the Tyrrhenian Sea off the Sorrentine Peninsula, on the south side of the Gulf of Naples in the Campania region of Italy. The main town Capri that is located on the island shares the name. It has been a resort since the time of the Roman Republic</string>
    <string name="florance">Florence (/ˈflɒrəns/ FLORR-ənss; Italian: Firenze [fiˈrɛntse] (About this sound listen))[2] is the capital city of the Italian region of Tuscany. It is the most populous city in Tuscany, with 383,084 inhabitants in 2013, and over 1,520,000 in its metropolitan area.</string>
    <string name="pisa">Pisa (/ˈpiːzə/; Italian pronunciation: [ˈpiːsa; ˈpiːza]  is a city in the Tuscany region of Central Italy straddling the Arnojust before it empties into the Ligurian Sea. It is the capital city of the Province of Pisa. Although Pisa is known worldwide for its leaning tower (the bell tower of the cities cathedral), the city of over 91,104 residents (around 200,000 with the metropolitan area) contains more than 20 other historic churches, several medieval palaces and various bridges across the Arno. Much of the cities architecture was financed from its history as one of the Italian maritime republics.</string>
    <string name="roma">Roma [ˈroːma]) is the capital city of Italy and a special comune(named Comune di Roma Capitale). Rome also serves as the capital of the Lazio region.With 2,873,874 residents in 1,285 km2 (496.1 sq mi),[2] it is also the countries mostpopulated comune. It is the fourth-most populous city in the European Union by populationwithin city limits. It is the centre of the Metropolitan City of Rome</string>
</resources>

